rvnetwork.com 2009-06-19

# Generally, personal information is not collected from visitors to the Escapees Discussion Forum website

**Escapees Discussion Forum Privacy Policy**

Generally, personal information is not collected from visitors to the Escapees Discussion Forum Website. However, in order to access certain special services, personal information is requested; those cases are described in more detail below.

**Bulletin Board Registration** ****

The Escapees Discussion Forum requires a valid e-mail address for users who want to participate in the discussion forums. This allows us to protect our community from abusive postings and provides a verifiable point of contact should legal questions arise. At any time, you have the ability to keep your e-mail address hidden from other users by selecting that option within your user profile.

Also, in the forum registration, you have the option of providing some additional information such as occupation, interests, and home-page URL. This information is made available to other bulletin board users to foster a sense of community. If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave the fields blank, and your registration will still be processed.

**Bulletin Board Notices** ****

From time to time, the forum administrator may send out notices regarding the Escapees Discussion Forum Website. If you check "yes" on your registration form for this option, these occasional notices will be sent to your e-mail address. You can change this option at any time by clicking on the "profile" link and modifying your profile.

**Cookies** ****

Certain activities on the Escapees Discussion Forum Website involve the use of "cookies" to facilitate your experience. This includes retention of your username and password for the forums to make logging in easier. You have the option to turn these cookies off at any time by updating your user profile preferences. If your browser doesn’t support cookies, or if you have cookies turned off, these preferences will not be set.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

The Escapees RV Club does not disclose personally identifying information collected online to any third parties, except where specifically required by law. Your e-mail address and other personal information will never be sold to third parties for any reason. All reasonable care is taken by staff handling personal information to ensure its security.

It is also important to be aware that when you voluntarily provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a posting on the bulletin board, that information is publicly available and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage the offering of any personally identifying information within your postings on the message board itself.
